2026-06-16 | feat: implement api routes and migration scripts while updating environment dependencies and documentation
2026-06-12 | feat: initialize database schema, project structure, and anti-spoofing migration scripts
2026-05-11 | update model and push all file
2026-05-05 | feat: implement device binding workflow, biometric admin unlock, and updated system documentation
2026-04-28 | update sistem
2026-04-16 | firs commit
2026-04-15 | Face recognation
2026-04-15 | first commit
